team in general system.
But I'm going to group a guy that I had the opportunity to be blessed to work with.
We'll start with our 125,000.
We'll try.
Let's go.
Come on.
Line up across here.
We'll go ahead and sit here.
Come on over here and line up.
We'll try to make up Jack's deck.
There are 133,000 in older brother.
So he's car set with a hundred, 41,000.
Or 149,000.
There's pinned the lead.
I mean, the attachment you give it to you.
You've got to start even dreaming about him.
I have to drink with this showman.
Think you're out and show you the hair.
I have a dream.
It's hair and a drone.
All the way down to a questionable style.
I'm dying.
It is good moms.
Let's make sure you get that trim back.
I think they're all along the beard you go to.
We're 165 pounds wide, Jordan.
And all these young men are national qualifiers.
Which is why we're only brought 10 of them.
And I'll kind of explain a little bit in detail here in a second.
We're 174 pounder down the crawl.
Our 184 pounder is Alex Kaufman.
Our 197 pounder is another Z.
Just a little bit different size ZXO.
And our big way at the end there are anyway is Brian.
Also brought with us are two assistant coaches.
Casey Malm.
And Mark Hoppton.
I'll just go a little bit quick.
We'll talk about some.
We won't go in detail.
In order to qualify for the national tournament.
We had to make it through a 10 team.
Regional.
All these guys ended up in the final.
We got six regional champions.
We had four runner-ups from that.
Then we got the national tournament.
We had nine all-American.
Which is to be an all-American place in the top eight.
Very fortunate to turn in that very good situation for all of them.
We also have the most falls reward with our 125 pounder.
We've got two drive-in.
Please or not, he didn't make 125 pounds a month ago.
I don't know how, but I look at how to write now.
But everybody here is a form.
We're like, well, I wish you was an opportunity.
And you have to be in that space to bring the whole team down.
Because the whole team is just an exceptional group of young men.
And he's getting their up here represented with our coaching staff.
And everything else.
I'm just honored to be a part of it.
It's been a great ride.
But I want to draw a special attention to life's work.
Life's work with the national finals for the last year, the last year, the last year.
The last year.
We came up a little bit short.
We got a second.
But the year before he was a national champion.
And everybody in this group, like I said, I can't brag on him enough.
And I'm very, once again, just very fortunate for the opportunity to date.
We've left us with to bring a national title to any of you, and to the community of my
Emma, and thank you for everything that you guys have done.
Coach, thank you.
We've got, and I know we're going to do this later in the week at the college also.
I believe we are.
But there's a proclamation here, and I'm going to ask Councilman Johnson to do the honors
of reading this.
I know that he's worked with Dr. Haley on helping to arrange this, and so I'm going to ask
him to read that if he can find that he's got his reading glasses on.
I'm ready.
I'm in the proclamation declaration of April 3rd, 2018, as 2019, the O&M wrestling team
day, and I say to my Emma, Ottawa County Oklahoma, we're at Mayor Rudy Shelter, and the
Miami City Council of Labor is important to recognize citizens who are just saying we're
going to tell us about various means, and it makes significant contributions to our community.
And we're at the Miami City Council of Labor that the 2018, the O&M wrestling team, or such
individuals, worthy of being in knowledge, and we're at the 2017, and the 2018, and the
2019, the O&M wrestling team, produced a 14-in-1 dual record, and we're at the 2017, 2019,
the O&M wrestling team, was a national runner-up at the Nation-Doo Championship, and
we're at the 2017, 2018, the O&M wrestling team, won the West, and termed history of championship
for the 5th consecutive year.
We're at the 2017, 2018, the O&M, the O&M wrestling team produced non-in-all Americans, both
driving, Jack Carster, Carcetta, Carcetta, Cody Carcetta, Candidly, Y Jordan, Devon
Crow, Alex Colton, Zincelvin, and Brian Andrews, but get them right.
We're at Coach Ramfero in the A&M, the O&M, the third national title in the past five years
at A&M, the O&M, and we're at Coach Joe Ramfero, the national coach of the year, where
the sixth time in his last year's coaching career.
Now therefore, be it all resolved, that my research in the Miami City Council, the year declared
to the April 3rd, 2018, as 2018, and the O&M wrestling team, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M,
the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the O&M, the
All right, thanks guys very much.
All right, scroll through.
Appreciate it.
I don't know.
Good thing you're saying for me.
Hey, I'll hang around if you look for a minute.
Yeah, just a little bit.
Just a little bit.
You guys can go this way.
We should hang around.
I don't want that.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thanks, Doug.
So besides these awesome group of wrestlers that
are currently residents of Miami as students of
any, we have a former resident of Miami that we also
want to recognize.
And I'm going to ask you to read this one too.
Sure.
If you would.
Bill, could you come up with that?
We've got.
You've got it.
We'll go ahead.
You've got to stand in line for Dr. Hill, please.
Okay.
Great.
Promotivation.
Declaration of April.
Third, 2018.
You're out here today in the city of Miami.
I'll be counting up the home.
We're as mayor Rudy Shelton.
I'm city council.
I'm living as important to recognize citizens.
They're distinguished themselves by various means.
And they'll make significant contributions to our community.
And where's my city council?
I believe that he, you know, I hail as such an individual.
Worthy of being in knowledge.
And whereas in 2013, you know, I hail when the couple home of
class 4x10 tile.
As a senior.
I'm a high school.
Whereas you know, I hail when the M.I.A.
postseason tournament championship.
And whereas Mark 10th of 2018.
And see the rapids up.
I will.
You'll I hail when the NCAA division 2 championship.
And whereas you like I hail, it became a 44th individual national champion.
And the university.
Central.
Almost wrestling history.
Whereas you'll I hail.
It was maybe the end.
I, a wrestler of the year.
Following the 24 and out.
Seas.
Now they're important to be a result.
That mayor shows in the United States Council.
Do you hear about the clerk?
Trace the apple third.
2019.
Does he like to die in the city of Miami?
Yeah.
You're going to hear about the number.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Very well, sir.
Yes.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
Okay.
Item 3 is a proclamation declaring April 8th.
Through the 14th, 2018.
National 911 telecommunicator week.
And I've got a proclamation.
I'm going to read this one.
Whereas 911 is nationally recognized as the number to call in the emergency to receive immediate
help from police, fire, emergency medical services or other appropriate emergency responsibilities.
And whereas 911 was designated by Congress as a national emergency call number of the wireless
communications and public safety act of 1999.
Work.
As the enhanced nine-month one act of 2004, established enhanced nine-month one is a high national priority as part of our nation's home insecurity and public safety.
Whereas people of all ages use nine-month one is critical to educate the public of all ages on the proper use of nine-month one.
Whereas a growing segment of the population, including the deaf heart of hearing, deaf blind, and individual speech disabilities,
increasingly communicate with non-traditional text, video, and instant messaging communication services.
And anticipate that these services will be able to connect directly to nine-month one.
Whereas thousands of nine-month one calls are made every year by children properly trained in the use of nine-month one.
Resulting in live-save, which underscores the critical importance of training children early in life about nine-month one.
Whereas there's widespread misuse of the nine-month one system, including prank and non-emergency calls,
which can result in costly and inefficient use of nine-month one in the emergency response resources.
Now, therefore, be it resolved that mayor-sholes in this Miami City Council do hereby declare April 8 through 2014.
2018 is national nine-month one telecommunicator week within the city of Miami.
In witness wherever I have hearing to set my hand.
And I know we have some emergency responders here tonight, or nine-month one people.
But if you would, if some of them would introduce them because I apologize I don't know every one station.
Or if you want to introduce yourselves.
Chief?
And it.
The next one is passed out there.
We can't say enough about our dispatcher.
They work short-handed.
We're under staff in the position to have two full-time dispatchers 24-7.
And they just do an absolutely incredible job.
This that's advisor to nine-avenants.
Dispatch trainer.
Right?
And that's where you told me.
Nine-avenants.
And dispatcher.
Debrit.
And I can never pronounce what.
Ender record.
Very fast.
But we're very proud of our dispatchers.
They do an absolutely incredible job.
And probably most critical job in high city.
And it is for workforce, me, MS, and finance.
Absolutely.
Okay.
Well, I'm going to present this to you, Donna Anna.
And we've got a lot to do.
Okay.
Item four is public input on schedule personal appearances.
And when you audience it wishes to address the council on any of the agenda items.
Item 5 is the consent agenda staff is recommending item 6 through 10, which are claims minutes,
garage sale resolution, and monster truck rental of the fairgrounds, and JAR Cemetery
maintenance service contract. Do we have a motion to approve the consent agenda as recommended?
We have a second. Second.
roll call please?
Aye.
Item 11 is considering the resolution of proving the incurring of debt in debt against the Miami special.
Do you tell the authority as the agenda item that we dealt with earlier when Greg was up?
Do we have a motion to approve the indebtedness?
Yes, motion.
roll call please?
Aye.
Item 12 is discussion of an ordinance and the Miami special utility authority resolution,
freezing transfers out of the MSUA fund to finance bonds, for MSUA capital improvements,
per the recent well-danned rate study, Tyler and Jill.
And that's electric only so far instead.
Now, in the right study, what was provided for in the rain creases are actually 20 billion
dollars worth of improvements.
An 8 million dollar, an 9 million dollar, a 7 million, a 50,000 dollar, a million billion
a million billion trillion.
In the VA, if you're going to the next, actually the third page, that's best actually to
rate increases through 2021.
Okay.
So, this is a list of all the capital improvements that we're looking at.
There's the nickel substation.
Right here is the Operator and Operations Center.
So, these are the capital improvements for the 23 million.
I just talked about the 8 million are going to fund.
This is one to five years for 10 million.
or the two, they'll cross over to the second,
see what's that nine million bombin' that we'll do next time.
So, we were looking at transphars and I just put down
the transfers that are known in SUA transfers.
So, just for gentle operation,
it's 2.28 health insurance fund,
and this is back from FY 1670.
So, he came up with the 4.1 million in the right study,
based on these transfers.
So, that's where I keep saying the 4.1 is what these be friends
and it's from this right study of these transfers at FY 1670.
For this year, we actually use the,
we kept that number the same.
So, we are living within that number.
In the current fiscal year.
Yes, they're in 19 correct.
So, there's two things that you could do
to free transfers.
The MSU-I could do a resolution,
and if you go to the next page,
the meat of the resolution is right here.
It just says the authority here by limits transfers
out of the MSU-I fund 510 for a specific dollar amount,
annually as annual budget requirement,
and less than specific to the floor,
MSU-I infrastructure or capital improvements.
That's just proposed language, just for discussion.
Another draft ordinance I created for the council,
it's actually based upon the street valley ordinance
that was approved.
It's ordinance over 1562.
It talks about the roadway,
and that the city manager is to provide a budget
that has no less than 500,000 in the for road maintenance
in the street valley.
So, this kind of ordinance,
the street valley doesn't mean that it has to be 500.
That means you can propose it, and you guys can change that number.
You can double it, you can make it zero, whatever you want,
but he has to propose that your sheet has to propose 500,000 in the roadway.
So, I just mirror that language, and I said the city manager
shall provide for no more than a specific dollar figure,
and my mind did be 4.1 million in exchange
in transfer outside MSU-I, same language as the resolution,
and less than 4 infrastructure or MSU-I capital improvements.
Now, another option that I don't
know, we get some thought on it, was maybe a percentage.
However, the right study, the revenues,
you're going to go up every year, because we're designed to.
We've approved of to go up to pay for these 20, 30 million dollars in the funding.
However, we, his numbers are conservative.
So, I'm assuming his numbers will, our kids are in the numbers.
So, whatever he says, we're going to make a little bit more,
because that's what he said historically,
and that's what he said he'd deal with this great study.
So, I just kind of gave you a, I took,
our actual revenues from 16.
And this MSUA, so MSUA's actual renderer was 21.8 million.
So, that is a 19%, so 4.1 million is 19% of what the renderers were in 1670.
This year, the budgeted, which we have finished the year, so it's just an estimated number,
we're estimated 24 million, and that's a 17% of 4.1 million would be.
And then projected, this is what I did, this BA, of course, that number is going to change almost daily,
but right now it's at 17%.
So, I didn't know if you wanted to, you know, I've tried to give you a second option,
and there may even be a third option out there, that you guys could suggest.
Or, if you want us to look, this design, we can do that too.
We just felt it was important enough to, because we saw it in that right side, it was an eye over us.
I'm just, this won't journal hurting things, of course.
So, like, keeping their evidence in the utility system, whenever you go far,
it looks like they can't consideration on the readiness system.
They're saying they look favorably on things like this.
Yes.
Can anybody, will it make it, you know, an actual raid, one that will get us properly knocked.
You know, it might make it a difference between the stable and optimistic,
and then the future.
So, again, it's not just trying to hurt anything that happens to you.
So, Jill, I was a little confused about number two in number three,
based on budget and based on projected, or you just saying that we're pretty much on target.
The projection is, I mean, it's a little higher than budget, but is that why?
I think it's just one sure, I understand the distinction between.
It's a budget of number, and so now, as a budget of this VA,
our projected revenue for 1819 is 24.5.
So, both of those were half to 17% rounded.
Yeah.
It just happened to have about 70%.
Okay.
Comparing option two, it's one to two.
If we freeze that in, if we put it at a percentage, that could be a different percentage,
it could be a moving target, right?
Right.
Which concerns us a little bit, because we just actually talked about that in the afternoon,
because the rates are supposed to go up.
The revenue to fund the things that were proposing.
That list about it.
Sorry, they're point there as if you...
But as the rates go up, your percentage goes down.
Well, if you said, okay, it's going to be 19% from now on.
Well, the rate of revenues are going to go up, so it's going to be 19%, so it's going to be a bigger bit.
But the dollar amount would grow in that case if you froze.
if you throw the dollar amount, it's not, it's not variable.
And so I think Jill's point of maybe what you were getting at Vicki was where these
right increases are in place to fund those improvements. If we take 19% let's just say we
put 19. If we take 19% of the increasing amount every year then that could potentially
the short changes. Is that, it's not a certainty that it would, but it potentials.
It could, if things were tight.
Yeah, if you get that you get a third option, if I did kind of wreck my right turn, if I did
that third option? Whatever we do, future accounts can change, right?
I mean these are just here to hear, but basically we're saying this is our position, this
is kind of our philosophy and it's subject to change at any point. Brian, I know you've brought
this up a couple of times. What are you thinking?
Well, I'm going to have to digest a little bit, tell you know, I kind of had some concerns,
but it's been a step that you guys talked about. My biggest concern was always I just hated
this to rob from utilities, especially when we're having to go and get this money. So whenever you
if we received a big expansion of some form that came in and our utilities was,
are that number going to go up, my fear is I don't want to just, because we get this big,
we let's not put that back into our utilities. I want to still have a percentage that goes into our
a set percentage that we don't steal from. So they know what they can work with. So.
And as is what Jill is providing you, especially this option about the number is kind of how we're approaching
the budget. Currently we're putting together the 1819 budget and our discussions.
Both last year and this year we're saying let's try to freeze transfers at this number.
Recognizing that it is a fluid situation that numbers move and it does put a lot of pressure on our
budgets and puts pressure on our expenditures. There's no two ways about it that what government
unit doesn't have those pressures. Okay. So this really more or less codifies what we're talking
about internally quite a bit. And I think you've had that exact concern is what is the guideline,
well the guideline is our conversation by adopting an ordinance like this the guideline is more in
in place that everybody understands. Now can it be changed or situations change or something like that
absolutely, but at least it gives all of us that guideline and understanding is what you want us to do.
And if it's going to be changing the future there's we can be confident there's going to be a
conversation about why this was done the way it was. So the future council is going to understand
what the thing is. It's not something that would just be done without consideration and thought.
And I think of the past.
I remember right do we have we have percentages upwards of 24% with that?
And what we were trying to do is stabilize that because what we've seen is that we might have one fiscal year,
where it's huge and another fiscal year, where it goes down exactly.
So now we're just trying to keep it in a much steadier position.
And so just to restake what I believe the will to hand assumptions were when you
talking about that there was a straight line that's same amount.
Those were the transfers out.
So he's predicated his rating increases on a growing balance.
But out of that growing balance, the same amount coming out each year.
And so that incremental increase is to pay for the improvements that's set.
Right.
And so you're tonight or not in a certain night, tonight you're saying,
think this through and hopefully be prepared to give us some guidance for long because
you're in the middle of the budget process.
On that note, do you have a budget calendar prepared yet where you've backed down from
here's the approval date?
Yes.
Okay.
Because I know we you mentioned budget meetings earlier.
Probably we'll probably have some discussions with you about the budget at the end
of this month.
Then we'll probably have our actual budget meetings in May getting geared up for any changes.
And of course, the adoption is in June for having it ready by July 1.
Correct.
And you know, individually you've talked to me about wanting to have something like this and
to credit, Jill and Tyler, they were already working on something.
So I think we're putting together by doing this what you were hoping we would be able to do as
well.
So I'm kind of happy we're able to get this to you as quickly as we've been able to.
Tyler, do you feel a little bit better about that discussion?
In the utility side?
I bet you do.
I do.
I feel better about it.
Right.
I need some guidance.
Can you tomorrow circulate that kind of budget schedule?
Because everybody needs to be looking at their calendars if we're going to have some.
Why do I need to wait for the 10 index for the first two of the budget work sessions
for the discussion, the initial discussion?
May you're April.
Okay.
So.
What do you do those?
Yeah.
Those are just the 10 of discussion.
You're all right.
Is one of those are regular work sessions anyway?
Yes.
So this is third.
Yeah.
I do think that unless there's some initiatives that you have that you want us to start
considering the way we're approaching this budget is very much a status quo budget.
From.
what we're trying to do this fiscal year, carrying it forward.
That doesn't mean we're not doing anything.
You saw what we're doing by way of approach on the comprehensive plan.
But I don't think we have any new initiatives or anything like that that we're really working on right now.
We just anticipate kind of status quo going into the next fiscal year.
We have a lot going on.
Oh, do we ever?
So the council members, if there are any different areas of emphasis or, you know, what?
Let me know that.
So it would be discussed at that work session at the lab.
Absolutely.
The idea is for things that we want to see staff doing.
Beyond that, just please come to that meeting prepared to kind of give, you know,
we'll talk about it again.
We want to have our thoughts on it so we can share it with staff.
And if you'll send that schedule out of jail, sir, but it can kind of mark it on the calendars.
Okay.
Anything else on that item?
All right.
Thank you, guys.
Item 13 is purchased a view hardware to replace the network storage array for the city of Miami.
Dave.
Well, David's coming up to the podium.
I just wanted to say that normally an item like this, we might have put on the consent agenda.
But David, this is a project he worked in over a month on.
And I think it's a tremendous work that we're doing in our network system.
I thought it'd be good for David to be able to explain it to you and show him what he's up to.
Okay?
Yeah.
The hardware that is the hardware that is the hardware network infrastructure is what all of our servers sell.
So everything that runs into each other has been the meter inside of things, live on this hardware.
And I think it was saying I spent about six months working with a number of different vendors to find out what would that seem to see.
The reason for switching as a current system is what they consider in the service office.
Which means the hardware manufacturer will no longer support it.
So it's something broke.
We need to have to find third-party funds to fix it.
Or go at me and do this and buy something to rebuild.
David, how old is our current?
I believe it is six years old.
That seems to be the standard length of time.
The hardware manufacturer will warrant you these types of equipment.
I should note part of this amount.
Also, it includes three years of 24-7, four hours support.
So this is something that I think breaks in the middle.
call someone. And by the next morning I can have either everything fixed or I can actually
have the parts or whatever's required to get it back up and right.
There's one of the other big things on this with our current system being going on six years
old. The hardware is fairly editing. I mean if you think about it, I suppose computer equipment
was available in two that in twelve versions of what they were today. There's going to be a
ninety-day difference on the performance side of things. So I think it's actually going
to help the city to be able to work a little bit more efficiently and a little bit faster.
Of the three visits they sent in. I went with the one that was in the middle because the second
bid that came to me. That's the 48th of the liquid which is a low-volt number. They put in there
to try to come in with a super-low option. But it would be kind of like going and getting the
cheapest quality equipment because it's just a bit of it. The one from that in the work group was an excellent
bid. It was quite a bit more expensive and what they were wanting to do is replace a lot more. Then
what we were really needed to continue to maintain what we were going. And like I said, the bid
one is the one that I think we should approve because it's going to give us equipment that will be under warranty
for three years and at the end of the three years we can pay about $11,700 to $4. It's a bit back
to warranty for an additional three years. So we know if we go with this right now three years
or not that's what it's going to cost to warranty for additional three years.
What was the one number two? The warranty on number two, I have not 200 years. I got a print
of that. So I would say the warranty for number two is a four-hour. It's also going to be
a three-year and it came in six thousand six hundred and forty-four dollars to actually want to
get the same line. So is that the second three-year cost in this 78,000 and the end of 48 are they built
into that. Second three years, so three years from now we would be. So the 78 includes the 11,000
and the 48 includes the six thousand and then there's a renewal option after three years on that.
And so there's about a $30,000 difference between AOS is one and two bid and five.
thousand of that being the award he cost so there's 25,000 in I would
not I guess quality difference and also additional hardware.
On the of the difference in cost, the one that came in at 48,000 was for an
already that was actually a nimble storage array which is that it's a main
with actually they're one of the companies that make storage array.
What they have done is they have taken traditional hard drives and some of the
newer hard drives, the solid safe drives and they've mixed those together and
I still still so they can provide it much safer but less.
Well, something that doesn't have as good a requirement.
I mean it gets to job done but it's kind of it's it's it's very apparent
with if you've got them tied by side and you're using them to see the one that
78,000 is actually a I believe it was Cisco as well as a it was an old
financial array as well as they even have a list is for the company of manufacturers.
The main difference they're being it's actually to be a little bit faster it's going to
be a lot less likely to be thrown to failure the one thing I'm
not the older hard drives that are traditional to have the players they have a
life expectancy because there's a lower and there's a spender and you know,
7200 or you have all the time.
This confirms they just doesn't have that.
Basically just ones and zeros and a chip so they're likely to failure much more.
So this is a little off topic but we'll what difference will the bolt band with increase
make or we are we already have that here I can't or we'll be working on that here now we have
the bolt band with here in the building and this building is building and we have actually
one of the things we've done over the last years we're currently about to tie in the
airport in the solid way building to the network it's here on bolt we've already done the
CBB those fire stations the waste we're going to treat that plant as well as the
option of it we're building so we'll really only have the full cemetery and the travel
information center that's not usually the end and it comes out of the side so besides the
reliability of the solid state product versus the other and I would assume I would guess
it's a longer life yes the way they look at the life solid state drives is a little differently
they look at the number of trans
transactions that can do, basically going back and forth from one to the zero over its
life.
And it's in the petabytes of data, which it would be something like 100 billion transactions.
It's a huge number.
And usually they're guaranteed that they won't fail for 5 to 10 years, where it's standard
drive.
You're pretty much guaranteed that they're going to start failing in about 30 years.
So, I guess what I'm thinking in a West Coast store, if you've got a customer standing
in front of you and you're on the computer, if the refresh rate is such that there's
a one-second lag between your transaction or a 10-second lag.
I mean, that starts to become a problem.
I can pay for a lot more expensive communication lines and get that down to a 10-to-second,
but it's not cost-effective to do.
So, I guess that's kind of what I'm wondering here is the difference in the 48 and the 78.
What is a practical matter is the difference going to be?
I think a practical matter is the big difference there is.
I think if in relation to what you were talking about the amount of time it takes, the 48,
that's another one would be more educational, say, if we went, it's hard to explain.
And if you go to open a program or if you go to move something off the one or I'm doing
another drive, it might take 25 or 30 seconds depending on the side.
Whereas on the one that's the 78, that's in hers and it would probably take more than two to three seconds.
And that's just because the way the data is handled is completely different.
So, over time, you would notice a big difference in the speed.
I mean, it would be I know it's a little bit of just in days and days where it's possible.
Any other questions?
My concern, my concern is, I don't know we have to have a reason to accept a higher bid.
And what's that reason?
The reason the best reason I can give you is that's higher bid is a much better solution
because it's going to be less from the failure.
It's going to actually give us exactly what we asked for in the bid, where it's the one that was lower.
It was not 100% what we asked for in the bid, because in the way the hardware was kind of mixed together.
And now, I just, in my experience, it's something that's going to last the city and work the best for the next six years.
And this is something we won't replace for at least six years.
And is this money in the budget?
Yes.
We actually initially had a budget that was closer to been three amounts taken when I started the
process.
That's what most of the numbers were coming in.
And I worked with a number of people when people were calling the ask and me about the
big booths I was going to like.
Yeah.
And these are making many of them because I was trying to save as much as possible as I could
see.
Okay.
So I'd like you to have a bit of insight into it if you don't mind.
I'm okay with the fees okay with the money.
Yeah.
Did you hear the question that you exchange?
I've been following along.
Okay.
Don't see particular problems.
So, and you recommend this?
Yes.
All right.
So, do we have a motion to approve item 13, which is a purchase of new hardware?
Any motion?
And a second?
Roll call please?
Aye.
Thanks David.
Item 14.
Capital Ventures.
Government Relations LLC claimed for our April claim for 3000.
This is Stuart that's doing the workforce with flooding issues.
And we're also trying to work on some infrastructure stuff.
I know this is on here every month.
I just want to remind everyone what that is.
Do we have a motion to approve?
And a second?
Second.
Roll call please?
Aye.
Joseph.
Thank you.
Item 15.
Construction Manager at Risk Contract Approval with Magnum Construction.
Aye.
On the VA.
This tells you just, I mean, I get a real quick of what it is that they're going to be doing for us.
You can scroll with this a little bit.
This is their cost of work.
And we did question to make sure that they were comparable to what it was.
If you send us several sheets on where they were comparable.
And because we've kind of tried to compare them to.
Alicia, you've got one introduced?
Yeah.
Who is this?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's like...
There it is.
Roller.
Your people will be our construction.